是什么天惊地动的大消息 要我们马上赶过来？
So, what's the big news you had us rush all the way over here for?
我们要宣布的消息就是公司要我去土尔沙带领新的分公司
Our news. My company has asked me to head up our office in Tulsa.
所以从星期一开始 我已经正式被调职了
So as of Monday, I'm being officially relocated.
- 猩 我的天  - 什么？星期一？
- Oh, my God!  - What? Monday?
- 你得要去多久呢？- 他们说有可能会长达一年
- How long do you have to go for?  - They said it could be up to a year.
- 一年？- 那你也要去吗？
- A year?  - Well, do you have to go?
我似乎是没有选择 不是吗？
Well, I kind of have to, don't I?
都是因为这个愚蠢的东西
Because of this stupid thing.
再也没有比爱妻的支持更棒的东西了
There's nothing like the support of your loving wife, huh?
等一下 你不能去土尔沙
Wait a minute. Wait, you can't go to Tulsa.
也许你忘了 但是下星期我们要去看球赛的
Maybe you forgot, but we have tickets to the Jets game next week!
我很抱歉 但是我想我可能去不了
I'm sorry, but I don't think I'll be able to make it.
但是我们是要去看球赛耶
But we were gonna go see the Jets!
你不能离开我们 你就像是维系这个圈子的灵魂人物
You can't go. I mean, you're the glue that holds this group together.
- 真的吗？- 不是你
- Really?  - Not you.
我真不敢相信你们要搬走了
I can't believe you guys are moving.
- 我承接他们的公寓  - 不行
- I call their apartment!  - No!
- 咖啡来了 瑞秋  - 谢谢你 乔伊
- Here you go, Rach.  - Thank you, Joey.
你知道吗？我不确定可不可以喝有咖啡因的东西
You know what? I'm not even sure I can have caffeine.
我养育班还有凯萝的经验告诉我一杯咖啡不会影响你的母乳的
I went through this with Ben and Carol. One coffee won't affect your milk.
为了安全起见我要打电话给维纳医师
Just to be sure, I'm gonna call Dr. Wiener.
这么哼洇吗？
Every time?
没有必要每次有问题都打电话给他 好吗？
You don't have to call him whenever you have a question, okay?
- 相信我 我是有经验的  - 好吧 我相信你
- Trust me. I know this.  - All right. I trust you.
我看到你在拨电话 我不了解为什么…
I can see you dialing. I don't understand why...
我在讲电话 维纳医师吗？
I'm on the phone! Dr. Wiener?
看到罗斯跟瑞秋有了小孩 真是奇怪 好像大人
It's so weird seeing Ross and Rachel with a baby. It's just so grownup.
我知道 是啊觉得好像我们都一起长大了
I know, yeah. I feel like we're all growing up.
有人的名字叫"维纳(香肠)"真是笑死我了
A person named "Wiener." God, that kills me.
- 瞧瞧你就像个大人  - 事实上 你知道吗？
- Look at you all grownup.  - Well, actually, you know what?
我的确是长大了 知道吗？
I am, you know?
跟瑞秋发生的那件事让我意识到…
Well, that whole thing with Rachel made me realize...
或许我已经准备好要接受更认真的交往了
...that maybe I'm ready for a more serious relationship, you know?
我想要找一个…善良 成熟 稳重的女孩子
Like, I'd like to meet a nice, mature, commitment-minded lady.
外表并不是非常…
And looks aren't as important as...
不 她一定要很辣才行
Nah, she's gotta be hot.
我也许认识这样的人
You know, I might know somebody.
要不要你帮我找个对象 然后我们一起两对约会
How about you set me up with someone, and we double-date?
我可以啊 星期五怎样呢？
I can do that. Yeah. How's Friday?
- 没问题  - 好的
- Done!  - All right.
很好 真的？好 我们来看看
Good, really? Okay, let's see.
好的
All right.
你知道谁不错吗？珊蒂普霸
You know who's great? Sandy Poopack.
"普霸"？
"Poopack"?
好吧 没关系 那莱娜缓婉乐可能也不行了
Yeah. All right. Well, that rules out Lana Titwyler.
- 我有好消息  - 你不用去土尔沙了吗？
- I've got good news.  - You got out of the whole Tulsa thing?
好吧 我有新消息
Okay, I have news.
你不用跟我一起搬到土尔沙 你可以待在这里 保有工作
You don't have to move to Tulsa. You can stay here and keep your job.
太好了 是怎么回事呢？
That's great! How?
老板跟我达成一个协议 我一星期在土尔沙待4天就可以了
My boss and I worked out a deal where I'm in Tulsa four days a week.
所以另外二天我可以跟你在一起
So the other three, I can be here with you.
所以一星期有四天你不在？
So you're gonna be gone four days a week?
不行
No.
不好意思 你是不是太习惯说不行了呢？
I'm sorry, are you just used to saying that?
不是 我不能跟你分开那么久的
No. I can't be away from you for that long.
- 真的吗？- 是啊 你是我先生
- Really?  - Yeah, you're my husband.
我不要一年两百零八天跟你住在不同州
I won't live in a different state than you for 208 days out of the year.
算的真快 我们土尔沙的分公司可以聘请你的
That's fast math. We could use you in Tulsa.
谢谢你试着想出更好的方式 但是如果你要去土尔沙 我会跟你去
Thanks for trying to figure out a way, but if you go to Tulsa, I go with you.
你这样说的时候竟然没有做呕吐状
You said that without gagging.
真的耶
I know!
你说什么？
Well, excuse me?
哦？那你也去吃屎吧
Oh, yeah? Well, up yours too!
- 那到底是谁啊？- 维纳医师
- Who the hell was that?  - Dr. Wiener.
瑞秋 你不能在凌晨三点打电话给人家的
Rach, you can't call people at 3:00 in the morning.
你知道吗？你听起来就像他老婆一样
You know what? You sound just like his wife.
艾玛有怎样吗？
Was there anything even wrong with Emma?
当然是有怎样 好吗？我又不是疯了
Yes, of course there is! Okay? I'm not insane.
是怎样？
What was it?
打隔
Hiccups.
我告诉过你了 不能每次有鸡毛蒜皮小事都打电话给他
I told you, you can't call him every time any little thing comes up.
看来我是真的不能了 他不接我们了
Well, not anymore I can't. He fired us!
我们该怎么办呢？我们得再另找一个小儿科医师了
What are we gonna do? We have to find a pediatrician.
等一下 莫妮卡说你们小时候
Wait, Monica said that when you guys were growing up...
很喜欢你们的医师 他叫什么名字呢？
...you liked your doctor. What was his name?
葛曼医师吗？
Dr. Gettleman?
不 我认为这不是个好主意
Yeah, no, I don't think that's a good idea.
事实上 我想他死了
In fact, I think he's dead.
为什么坏事都发生在我身上？
Why does everything happen to me?
我保证 明天第一件事就是找到一个新的医生
I promise, first thing tomorrow, we'll find another doctor.
但是我要很早起床 而且我现在觉得不是很舒服
But I gotta get up early, and I'm not feeling well.
你不舒服？是怎么回事呢？德国麻疹吗？
You're not feeling well? What do you have? Rubella?
别靠近艾玛 她还没有注射预防针
Because don't go near Emma, she has not had that shot.
我仔细想想 感觉真像是德国麻疹
You know, come to think of it, it does feel rubella-like.
维纳
Wiener!
维纳 维纳 维纳
Wiener! Wiener! Wiener!
瑞秋
Rachel!
太棒了 现在他就知道那是我了
Great! Now he's gonna know it was me!
看我为今晚我们两对约会打扮如何？
So how is this for our big double date tonight?
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
太棒了 这正是我要的反应
Great. Just the reaction I was hoping for.
是啊 你有帮我找到人吗？你没有忘记吧？
Yeah, so you found someone for me? You didn't forget?
当然没有 你会爱死玛莉艾伦的
Of course not. And you'll love Mary Ellen.
她真的很聪明 可爱风趣 而且
She's really smart and cute and funny and...
我不能告诉你我是怎么知道的 但是她并不反对三人行
I can't tell you how I know this, but she is not opposed to threesomes.
好耶
All right.
- 说一点我的约会对象吧  - 不行
- So tell me something about my guy.  - No.
别这样 透露一点嘛 他叫什么名字？
Come on, give me something. What's his name?
- 麦克  - 麦克 好的 他姓什么呢？
- Mike.  - Mike. Okay, what's his last name?
可恶 就不能为浪漫而保有神秘感吗？
Damn it! Is there no mystery left in romance anymore? !
几个小时之后在餐厅与你跟麦克见
We'll see you and Mike at the restaurant in a couple hours.
好的 没问题 待会见 拜拜
All right, great. See you. Bye-bye.
我为什么要说麦克呢？根本不认识谁叫麦克的 为什么不说…？
Why'd I have to say Mike? I don't know a Mike! Why couldn't I have said...?
这里面根本就没有男生
There's no guys in there!
要找好医生真是好难 要如何分辨哪个是好医生
It's impossible to find a good doctor. How do you know the good ones...
哪个又会倪洹弟弟摩擦你的膝盖呢？
...from the ones who'll push their penis against your knee?
什么？
Excuse me?
我知道她的意思
I know what she's talking about.
我们要找新的小儿科医生
Well, we've gotta find a new pediatrician.
罗斯昨晚不舒服 艾玛或许也被感染到了
Ross was getting sick last night, and Emma may have caught it.
- 你为什么不去找葛曼医生呢？- 罗斯说他死了
- Why don't you see Dr. Gettleman?  - Ross said he died.
他没死我 上星期才遇到他女儿
He didn't die. I just saw his daughter last week.
她说他很好 但是她呢可被肉毒杆菌搞惨了
She said he was fine. Her, on the other hand, botched Botox.
太好了 那我要带艾玛去找他
Great. Well then, I'm gonna take Emma to see him.
为什么罗斯说他死了呢？
I wonder why Ross said that he died?
或许他把他跟他小时候的心理医生搞混了
Maybe he confused him with his childhood therapist.
他有心理医生？
He saw a therapist?
他以前常常做重复的噩梦 吓死他了
He used to have a recurring nightmare. It freaked him out.
哇 什么噩梦呢？
Wow, what was it?
梦到我要吃掉他
That I was going to eat him.
麦克
Mike!
怎样？
Yeah?
好了
Okay.
真不敢相信 我竟然跟你做这件事
I can't believe I'm doing this with you.
我才刚结束一段九年的恋情…
Although I did just end a nine-year relationship...
所以我应该敞开心胸迎接一些挑战
...so I should be open to taking some risks.
一切安啦 跟着我就没事 好吗？
Everything is gonna be fine. Follow my lead, okay?
你只要假装是麦克就可以了
All you have to do is pretend to be Mike.
- 我就是麦克啊  - 演的真不错
- I am Mike.  - Attaboy.
她们来了
Here they come.
- 我是菲比  - 菲比 这位是麦克 你好吗？
- I'm Phoebe.  - Phoebe. Mike. How you doing?
- 很高兴认识你  - 乔伊 这位是玛莉艾伦珍金
- Nice to meet you.  - Joey, this is Mary Ellen Jenkins.
麦克 你跟乔伊是怎么认识的呢？
So, Mike, how do you and Joey know each other, anyway?
我跟乔伊是怎么认识的呢？
How do Joey and I know each other?
如果每次有人间我这问题 我就有五块钱赚 那我就变富翁了
If I had a nickel for every time somebody's asked me that.
- 在学校认识的  - 我们在大学认识的
- From school.  - We met in college.
我是说高中
I mean high school.
那你们认识可久了 那你现在是做什么的呢？
You guys go way back, then. So, what are you up to these days?
- 我是律师  - 麦克 律师
- Well, I'm a lawyer.  - Mike, attorney at law!
- 事实上 我才刚放弃执业  - 什么？
- Actually, I just gave up my practice.  - What?
这种事你应该先跟我讨论的
That's the kind of thing you usually run by me.
我想要成为专业钢琴音乐家 如果现在不赶快做 就来不及了
I want to play piano professionally. If I don't do this now, I never will.
太好了 我喜欢音乐家胜过律师
Great. I like that better than the lawyer thing.
这就是为什么我等到现在才介绍麦克给你
Which is why I waited until now to introduce you to Mike.
你不是还以为他是律师吗？
You thought he was still a lawyer.
不 我并没有那样说 我们帮你点杯鸡尾酒吧
No, that's not what I meant. Let's get you a cocktail.
你在做什么呢？
What are you doing?
帮你在土尔沙找餐厅的工作
Looking for restaurant jobs for you in Tulsa.
真是窝心 有找到吗？
That's so sweet. Did you find anything?
- 速食外餐  - 什么都没有 是吧？
- Slim Pickins.  - Nothing, huh?
不 速食外餐 是家烤肉店
No. Slim Pickins. It's a barbecue joint.
他们在找厨师 事实上并不全然是"厨师"
They're looking for a cook. Actually, "cook" may be a bit of a stretch.
他们在找炒豆子的帮手
They're looking for somebody to shovel mesquite.
"速食外餐"？听起来真是不高级
"Slim Pickins"? That is so cheesy.
"布高吉"也有在征人
Well, So Cheesy also has an opening.
亲爱的 没关系 我认识一个叫南西的人
Honey, that's okay. I know this woman, Nancy...
她是专门帮餐厅猖人头的 她或许会知道一些职缺
...who's a restaurant biz headhunter. She may know something.
我真的是太感激你愿意跟我去
Can I say how much I appreciate you coming with me?
当我们抵达土尔沙我会带你去速食外餐吃大餐的
When we get to Tulsa, I am taking you for a great dinner at Slim Pickins.
那布高吉呢？
So Cheesy?
全猪餐厅呢？
Whole Hog?
在土尔沙要找到正式餐厅还真是不简单
It's gonna be tough to keep kosher in Tulsa.
嗨 南西吗？嗨 我是莫妮卡盖勒
Hi, Nancy? Hi, it's Monica Geller.
我很好 我需要在土尔沙找份工作
I'm good. Listen, I'm looking for a job in Tulsa.
是啊 因为我先生被调职到那边
Yeah, well, my husband's been relocated.
因为我爱他
Because I love him.
不 我不想要纽约的工作
No, I don't want a job in New York.
杰屋在找人？哦 我的天啊:
Javu's looking? Oh, my God!
他特别指名要我？哦 我的天啊
He asked for me personally? Oh, my God!
哇 我真的是太受宠若惊了
Wow, this is really, really flattering.
但是我要搬到土尔沙了
But I'm moving to Tulsa.
所以 请你告诉杰屋…
So, just, if you would tell Javu...
我接受这份工作
...l'll take it!
我是瑞秋葛林 我有帮艾玛预约看诊
My name's Rachel Greene. I have an appointment for Emma.
葛曼医生快看完病人了 他等一下就会出来
Dr. Gettleman is finishing up with a patient. He'll be out shortly.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thank you
我想你只是感冒了 没有什么严重性
I think you just have a cold. It's definitely not strep.
谢了 医生
Thanks, doctor.
- 要不要来根棒棒糖呢？- 还用问吗？
- Would you like a lollipop?  - Do you even have to ask?
他还活着
He is alive!
好奇怪 你跟乔伊认识这么久了
It's so surprising that you and Joey have known each other for so long...
而我却从没有听说过你
...and I've never heard about you.
因为我们有吵过架
That's because we had a bit of a falling out.
麦克开车撞到我妈
Mike hit my mom with a car.
- 才没 我没有  - 没关系 我已经原谅你了
- No, I didn't.  - That's okay. I have forgiven you.
现在我们又是朋友了 一切都很美好
Now we're friends again, and everything's great.
等一下 你妈还好吧？
Well, wait. Is your mom okay?
拜托 我们在讲话耶
Please, we're trying to have a conversation.
你在《我们的日子》中亲切多了
You're a lot nicer on Days of Our Lives.
《我们的日子》 怪不得你看起来有点眼熟
Days of Our Lives! That's why you look so familiar!
- 什么？- 什么？
- What?  - What?
什么？
What?
你们彼此不认识吗？
Do you not know each other?
我们当然认识 他是在玩我们高中常玩的游戏
Of course we do. He's playing a game we used to play in high school.
我们假装不认识 我们玩很多种游戏的
We pretend we don't know each other. We played all kinds of games.
你还记得有一次你因为太蠢而被我揍吗？
You remember that one where I punch you in the face for not being cool?
让我问你一个问题 乔伊有几个姐妹呢？
Let me ask you something: How many sisters does Joey have?
六个
Six.
你在搞什么鬼？我比了七个
What are you doing? I said seven!
乔伊 为什么你要介绍陌生人给我呢？
Joey, why did you set me up with a stranger?
因为我忘记了 我很抱歉
Because I forgot about our date. I'm so sorry.
我也很抱歉 还有要澄清一下 我没有开车撞他妈
I'm sorry too. And just to be clear, I didn't hit his mother with a car.
你真是太不应该了 我花这么多时间帮你找完美的对象
You are unbelievable. I spent so much time finding the perfect girl for you.
玛莉艾伦真的很聪明很可爱又很随便
Mary Ellen is really smart and cute and loose.
嘿 你别装了吧？
Who are you kidding?
你在街上随便捉个男的塞给我？
You find some guy off the street for me?
天啊 这真是太羞辱人了
God, this is humiliating!
我很抱歉 如果你不喜欢这一个我可以帮你找更好的
I'm so sorry. If you don't like this guy, I can find you a better one.
麦克？麦克？
Mike? Mike?
我要走了
I'm out of here.
很高兴认识你
It was nice meeting you.
- 你也要走？- 你说的出我的名字 我就留下
- You're leaving too?  - I'll stay if you can tell me my name.
再见
Have a good night.
我们明天就要走了 而你还有好多东西要打包
We leave tomorrow, and you still have a lot to pack.
你说得对
You're right.
或许我不应该去
Maybe I shouldn't go.
什么？
What?
南西告诉我有一个很棒的餐厅在征人 杰屋？
So Nancy told me about this job at this great restaurant, Javu?
离土尔沙不会太远
But it's just a little outside of Tulsa.
那是多远呢？
Well, how far outside?
曼哈顿远吗？
Manattan?
你要接受这份工作吗？
And you're thinking of taking it?
你之前说跟我在一起比任何工作都重要
Before, you said that being with me was more important than any job.
但我猜 现在是旧工作 我 新工作
But I guess now it's old job, me, new job.
我会想念这只手的
I'm gonna miss this hand!
我知道这很过份…
I know this is a lot to ask...
但是 天啊 这是千载难逢的好机会
...but, my God, this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
那你说无法忍受每星期4天要分开 是怎么回事呢？
What happened to "you can't live without me four days a week"?
如果你仔细想想4天并不是很长的时间
Well, if you really think about it, I mean, four days is not that long.
星期一你去上班前我会见到你…
I see you Monday before you go to work...
然后星期四晚上我也会见到你…
...and Thursday when you get back...
而我总是在星期二忙得很晚 所以如果你仔细想想…
...and I always work late on Tuesdays, so really if you think about it...
事实上只有分开一天而己
...it's really just one day.
而如果我们连一天都撑不住 我们真的是有大问题了
And well, if we can't make it one day, we got real problems, my friend.
- 我认为你应该接受这份工作  - 真的吗？
- I think you should take the job.  - Really?
当你开始像猴子一样鬼吼时 我就知道这对你一定很重要
I know it must be important to you when you start chattering like a monkey.
这是我听过最美好的形容了
That's the nicest thing anybody's ever said to me.
- 新医生怎样呢？- 我真的很喜欢他
- How was the pediatrician?  - I really liked him.
是啊 是啊 真的 真的 真的很不错
Yeah, yeah. It was really, really, really good.
- 你答应我不会说出去的  - 我知道
- You promised not to say anything.  - I know.
罗斯还在看他小时候的医生
Ross still sees his pediatrician!
我不在乎
I don't care.
真的吗？你还在看葛曼医师
Are you serious? You still see Dr. Gettleman?
他是医术高明的诊断师
He is a brilliant diagnostician!
诊断师还是医生叔叔呢？
Diagnostician or boo-boo fixer?
真的 你应该去看适合你的医生才对
Seriously, you gotta go to an appropriate doctor.
为什么？我知道这是有点怪 但是他是个很棒的医生 好吗？
Why? I know it's a little weird, but he is a great doctor, okay?
他知道我的病史
He knows my medical history.
而且每次我去看病他都非常的慎重其事
And every time I go in there, he makes a big deal.
你知道的"瞧 这是我最喜欢的病人"
You know, "Look, it's my favorite patient."
是不是在把体温计插到你嘴里之前说的呢？
Does he say that before he sticks his thermometer in your tushy?
我还记得有人把他的安全毛毯带到大学宿舍
I seem to remember someone bringing his security blanket to college.
那不是安全毛毯 那是壁毯
That was not a security blanket. That was a wall hanging.
它倒是没有被挂在墙上太久
It didn't spend much time on the wall!
对不起
Excuse me.
嗨 我原本就希望可以再遇到你 我们可以谈谈吗？
Hi. I was hoping to run into you. Can we talk?
当然
Sure.
我真的很抱歉 我实在太不好意思了
Look, I'm sorry, really. I'm so embarrassed.
真的 我是个还不错的人 你可以问我的保释官
Really, I'm a pretty nice guy. Just ask my parole officer.
很明显地 我并不是很风趣
Apparently, I'm not a funny guy.
那你为什么要这样做呢？
Well, why did you go along with that?
因为他说 我可以吃一顿免费的晚餐 不过并没有
Because I was told that I'd get a free dinner, which I didn't.
还有他说 我可以认识漂亮的女生 这倒是有
And that I'd meet a pretty girl, which I did.
那倒是真的
That's true.
那你告诉我的事有哪些是真的呢？
Well, is anything you told me about yourself true?
我的名字真的是麦克 还有我真的会弹钢琴
My name is Mike. And I do play piano.
- 证明给我看  - 这里并没有钢琴
- Prove it.  - There isn't a piano here.
那对真正的钢琴家不会是问题吧
That wouldn't stand in the way of a true pianist.
好吧
Okay.
你真的很棒
You are really good.
- 我会弹一点吉他  - 真的？太棒了
- I play a little guitar myself.  - Really? That's great.
- 你弹奏什么种音乐呢？- 像是重原音 有民俗风味的
- What kind of music do you play?  - Like acoustic, folksy stuff, you know?
但是我现在在制作伍佰的CD封面
But right now I'm working on a couple Iron Maiden covers.
或许 有空的话 我可以…
Do you think that, maybe, sometime, I could...
没关系的 来吧 约我吧
It's okay. Go ahead, ask me out.
好吧 你想 或许有空的话我可以约你出去吗？
Okay. You think, maybe, sometime I could take you out?
你真是让我一点心理准备都没有
You just caught me off guard.
好啊 我很乐意
Yeah, that would be nice.
瞧瞧 我两个最要好的朋友
Look at this! My two best friends!
不好意思 我不想要太八婆…
Excuse me. I don't mean to be a jerk...
但是那个长疹子的婴儿是在我后面进来的
...but the baby with the rash came in after me.
- 医生等一下就可以看你了 先生  - 我知道…
- The doctor will be right with you, sir.  - I hear you...
妈咪 我找不到华多
Mommy, I can't find Waldo.
游乐场吗？他在大象后面
What, the circus? He's behind the elephant.
哇 你的孩子一定也很迷华多
Wow. So your child's a big fan of the Waldo books too?
是啊 所以我也很熟
Yeah, that's how I know.
- 对了 我叫罗斯  - 嗨 我叫莎莉
- I'm Ross, by the way.  - Hi, I'm Sally.
没有戒指 所以我想你也是单亲？
So no ring. Can I assume you're also a single parent?
- 我是单亲没错  - 很难 对吧？
- I am a single parent.  - It's hard, isn't it?
根本没有可以社交的时间 要去哪里认识朋友呢？
There's no time for a social life. Where are you gonna meet someone?
我不知道 可以在小儿科医生那里认识人吧
Let's say, I don't know, you met someone in the pediatriciars office.
小罗斯？轮到你了
Rossie? We're ready for you.
是啊…
Yeah...
走吧 小罗斯 轮到我们了
Come on, Ross Jr. It's time to go in.
妈咪
Mommy.
妈咪 那个人是怎么了？
Mommy, what's wrong with that man?
嘿 是我帮你找到华多的耶
Hey, I helped you find Waldo!
- 太好了 你还没走  - 你去哪了？
- Good, you haven't left yet.  - Where have you been?
有事情在葛曼医师那耽搁了一下
I got held up at Dr. Gettlemars office.
有一个人吓坏了所有的人
There was some guy that freaked everybody out.
你正好赶上 我得要走了 兄弟
You got here just in time. I really have to go, buddy.
哦 真是的
Oh, man.
- 答应我一下飞机就打电话  - 当然 我爱你
- Promise to call me when you land?  - Of course I will. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
不要舌吻 你们 儿童不宜
Watch the tongue, people. We got a baby over here.
- 再见 钱德  - 再见
- Bye, Chandler.  - Bye.
- 再见 亲爱的  - 再见
- Bye, honey.  - Bye.
- 怎么了 乔伊？- 我很生气你要走
- What's the matter, Joe?  - I'm mad at you for leaving.
你知道吗？你什么都不会就最会抛弃人家
You know, you're nothing but a big leaver.
带着笨行李的负心汉
A big leaver with a stupid suitcase.
你是不是故意说一些气话让自己好过点呢？
Any chance you're trying to pick a fight to make all of this easier?
老兄 你真是太了解我了
Dude, you see right through me!
好了 那么…再见了 莫妮卡
Okay, well... Bye, Mon.
再见 罗斯 瑞秋
Bye, Ross. Rachel.
- 再见 艾玛  - 好了 拜拜
- Bye, Emma.  - Okay, bye-bye.
旅途愉快 好了 哦 天啊
Have a good trip. Okay. Oh, my God.
钱德 等一下
Wait.
应该是旧工作…
It goes old job...
新工作…
...new job...
然后是你
...and you.
那只不过是我要做的工作
This is just something I have to do.
我知道
I know.
我好爱你
I love you so much.
我也知道
I know that too.
别担心 我很快就会回来了
Don't worry. I'll be back before you know it.
是的 一切都不会变
Yes, it will be the same.
因为我就是知道
Because I know, that's how.
我保证
I promise.
你可以双重保证吗？
You double promise?
一下机就打电话给我
Call me when you land.
- 轮到我讲了吗？- 好的 再见
- Can I talk now?  - Okay, bye.
- 乔伊  - 他要登机了
- Joey!  - He had to board.